Guide to the John Howard Griffin Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XII. The Decade of the Sixties
  - Sunseries XII.1: General
    - Drummond, Dwight L. To John Howard Griffin, University of Michigan, 16 April 1962- 12 April 1966, (16 a.l.s., 1 t.l.s. (with related material) (Box 10, Folder 363)
      [.Historian; author of Antislavery, the history of lynching in the south; he was professor at the University of Michigan.
    - Smith, Lillian To John Howard Griffin, Clayton, GA, 3 Dec. 1961 - 28 July 1963, (10 t.l.s.) (Box 10, Folder 364)
      [Author of Strange Fruit, Killers of the Dream, One Hour. These are among the most profound letters Griffin. He had always been a fan of her novels--Strange Fruit had a deep effect on him which he discusses in Black Like Me--and long wanted to meet her. They visited twice at her Georgia home. During those visits and in their very personal correspondence, they discovered an uncanny resonance and deep affection. Like Griffin, she was a musician, a Southern novelist, and had high regard for everything French. Griffin says in one of his letters to her that he felt as if Lillian Smith and John Howard Griffin were twins, even though she was nearly twenty years his senior. They came from the same background, discovered their own inculcated racism in similar ways, and fought courageously against prejudice, especially in the south. Both were ostracized for their public stand and for their controversial books, both fiction and non-fiction. Also, both were ill a great deal of their lives, and speak very personally about these afflictions. Some of the strongest passages by Smith are about her own work and about the work of Griffin. Her insights into her own method and her brilliant readings of Griffin's books are highly edifying to any serious reader or scholar.
    - Griffin, John Howard To Lillian Smith, Mansfield, TX, 1 Nov. 1961 - 10 June 1964, (19 t.l. (carbon) (Box 10, Folder 365)
      [In some of these long letters, Griffin reveals himself as he does nowhere else but his own journals; the discussions of her books show him to be, if not a brilliant critic, a passionately intelligent reader. Smith's books were among Griffin's favorite, and she was one of the very few contemporary writers he bothered to read (he rarely read contemporary fiction because he feared he would become unconsciously imitative of other styles). Aside from the many rich aspects of this correspondence, I discovered in Griffin's letters the most revealing discussions about his true motivations for the writing of Black Like Me. Also, his attitudes and fears about his own writing in general. He trusted Lillian Smith as a person and respected her writing so far above his own that he took her word as gospel as far as evaluating his writing (most of which he never reread once it was published).
    - Smith, Esther & Paula Snelling To John Howard Griffin, Clayton, GA, 24 Oct. 1966 - 14 March 1971, (1 a.l.s., 2 t.l.s.) (Box 10, Folder 366)
      [Re. Lillian Smith
    - Titus, Joan To John Howard Griffin, New York & Berkeley, 20 Nov. 1969 & 8 March 1970, (2 t.l.s. (with related material) (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Smith, Lillian Address before the Herald Tribune Youth Foundation, New York, 6 March 1950, (5 page t.ms. (with her ms. corrections) (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Boyle, Sarah Patton To John Howard Griffin, Charlottesville, VA, 18 Nov. 1962 - 11 April 1978, (21 t.l.s., 8 6, t.p.c.s. 1, a.p.c.s. 1, a.n. (on card with image) 1 page, t.ms. (from her second book) ) (Box 10, Folder 369)
      [Author of The Desegregated Heart and For Humans Only; a Southerner like Lillian Smith and Griffin, she began their correspondence in 1963. Most of the letters from the 1960s, but she wrote him until 1978. Actually, her first correspondence to JHG was a postcard sent in November of 1962, thanking him for his review of The Desegregated Heart published in The Saturday Review
    - East, P. D. To John Howard Griffin, 1961-1968, (43 t.l.s., 24 postcards) (Box 11, Folder 370-372)
      [East, editor of The Petal Paper and author of The Magnolia Jungle. Readers of Black Like Me will remember P.D. East as the hilarious and courageous editor of The Petal Paper, a small Mississippi newspaper that began as part of the establishment and slowly turned into a radically satirical voice. This is without question the wackiest correspondence Griffin had with anyone. East's letters and postcards, except for a very few, are full of jokes and put-ons, even when he tells Griffin of his Mississippi miseries (which was nearly all the time!) Griffin's responses have his own brand of humor but do, in fact, carry some seriousness as well; they catalogue his involvement in the civil rights struggle during the 1960s -- ranging from anger and frustration to bawdy humor (whereas his letters to Lillian Smith reveal another aspect to Griffin's character -- more serious and thoughtful -- but all genuinely part of the man).
    - Morris, Willie To P. D. East, New York, 10 December 1963, (2 page t.l.s.) (Box 11, Folder 373)
      [Editor of Harper's Magazine. This letter is an insightful critique of East's second attempt at a novel after The Magnolia Jungle, A Cock for Asclepius (it was never published).
    - Griffin, John Howard To P. D. East., [Mansfield, TX], 1961-1970, (90 t.l. (carbon) (Box 11, Folder 374-378)
      [No doubt Griffin wrote East through 1967 or 1968 but did not keep carbons. Many of these letters are meant to poke fun at East (one begins "Dear Genius" and another "Dear Judas") but more than half contain serious discourses on racism.
    - United States. Postal Service. Deposition of John Howard Griffin in the P.D. East postal fraud investigation, Fort Worth, TX, 1 June 1970, (2 page photocopy (with related material) (Box 11, Folder 379)
    - Thompson, Father August To John Howard Griffin, LA, 1963-1980, (2 a.l.s., 46 t.l.s.) (Box 11, Folder 380-382)
      [A parish priest who, at the time of his correspondence with Griffin, was the only black priest in Louisiana. Their dialogue, published first in Ramparts and reprinted in The John Howard Griffin Reader, also appeared in the Sheed & Ward anthology, Black, White and Gray, edited by Bradford Daniel. Most of the 1963 letters from both men discuss their dialogue and the difficulty of its being published because of resistance from Fr Thompson's Bishop. Eventually, it was published--in three separate publications mentioned above--and Fr Thompson went on to assist Griffin with The Church and the Black Man, as an active member of the Black Priests Caucus.
    - Griffin, John Howard To Father August Thompson, Mansfield, TX, 1963, (10 t.l. (carbon) (Box 11, Folder 383)
    - Letters to Griffin and Father Thompson, [v.p.], 1963-1965, (5 t.l.s.) (Box 11, Folder 384)
    - Sheed & Ward To John Howard Griffin, New York, 17 January 1964, (1 page t.l.s., 1 page agreement (copy) (Box 11, Folder 385)
      [Re. Black, White and Grey
    - Edward Keating To John Howard Griffin, CA, 1962-1966, (27 t.l.s.) (Box 11, Folder 386)
      [Publisher of Ramparts, published many of Griffin's essays, photographs and the autobiography, Scattered Shadows (two chapters in 1963 and again in 1965). Griffin, who eventually became a Senior Editor of Ramparts, put Keating in touch with Thomas Merton, Jacques Maritain, Father August Thompson, Penn Jones ("The Strange Deaths After Dallas") and many other writers and photographers.
    - Ramparts To John Howard Griffin, CA, 1962/1963, (11 t.l.(signed Harry Stiehl & Reno Unger) (Box 11, Folder 387)
    - Ramparts To John Howard Griffin, CA, 1966 & 1970, (4 t.l.(signed Warren Hickle & Maureen Stock) (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - Subseries XII.2: The Ramparts Interview
    - McDonnell, Thomas P. Ramparts Interview [questions] for John Howard Griffin, Mattapan, MA, [1962], (4 page t.ms.) (Box 11, Folder 389)
      [The Interview which ran in 1963, is one of the finest interviews with Griffin (and an opinion expressed by Griffin also). McDonnell was an excellent interviewer, who also interviewed Thomas Merton; he was, as well, the editor of The Thomas Merton Reader.
    - Griffin, John Howard Responses to McDonnell's questions, [Mansfield, TX], [1962], (17 page t.ms (carbon) (Box 11, Folder 390)
    - Ramparts Interview, Mattapan, MA, [1962], (15 page photocopy) (Box 11, Folder 390A)
    - McDonnell, Thomas P. To John Howard Griffin, Mattapan, MA, 2 Aug. - 20 Sept. 1962, (4 t.l.s.) (Box 11, Folder 391)
    - Griffin, John Howard To Thomas P, McDonnell, Mansfield, TX, 6 Aug. - 4 Dec. 1962, (5 t.l. (carbon) (Box 11, Folder 392)
    - Geismar, Maxwell Postscript to: "John Howard Griffin: The Devil in Texas", Westport, NY, 12 Aug. 1965, (8 page t.ms.) (Box 11, Folder 393)
      [This essay was intended as a "Postscript" to Geismar's long essay on Griffin ("The Devil in Texas"--published in American Moderns, Houghton Mifflin, 1959); it was the first major criticism of Griffin's work; both the long essay and the postscript were published together as the introduction to The Griffin Reader.
    - Exchange of letters between its two Senior Editors, Maxwell Geismar and John Howard Griffin, concerning Geismar's essay on Griffin's work that appeared in that same issue. Ramparts, November 1965, (6 page photocopy) (Box 11, Folder 394)
    - Pire, Father Georges Dominique, O.P. To John Howard Griffin, (10 t.l.s., 1 a.p.c.s., 4 telegrams (with related material), 1 printed card (photo. of Pier with Robert Oppenheimer) (Box 11, Folder 395)
      [Received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1958 for his work in behalf of refugees and minority groups in the wake of World War II. He founded the University of Peace in Huy, Belgium and was the author of the collection, Building Peace, which featured Griffin's essay, "The Intrinsic Other".
    - Letters to Griffin from various people in Europe concerning both the University of Peace and the "Friends of Father Pire" Organization., [v.p.], 1965-1976, (13 letters, 1 publication (From Heart to Heart) (Box 11, Folder 396)
    - Father Illtud Evans, O.P. To John Howard Griffin, [v.p.], 17 March 1963 - 13 February 1970, (1 a.l.s., 8 t.l.s., 2 t.l. (carbons) (Box 11, Folder 397)
      [A progressive Catholic priest and writer who, like his friends Thomas Merton, Jacques Maritain, and Griffin, was critical of the Church as a slow-moving institution with regards to race relations.
    - Cleaver, Eldridge To John Howard Griffin, Soledad, CA, 11 March 1966, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 11, Folder 398)
      [A convicted felon, Cleaver was released from prison partly upon the recommendation of Griffin that he was a talented writer. Cleaver went on to become one of the leaders of The Black Panthers and wrote Soul on Ice.
    - Axelrod, Beverly To John Howard Griffin, San Francisco, CA, 8 & 20 October 1965, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 11, Folder 399)
      [Eldridge Cleaver's attorney
    - State of California. Youth & Adult Corrections Agency To John Howard Griffin, Sacramento, CA, 29 October 1965, (1 t.l. (signed Joseph A. Spangler) (with related t.l. carbon by Griffin) (Box 11, Folder 400)
      [Re Eldridge Cleaver's parole
    - Pan African Association To John Howard Griffin, Baldwinsville, NY, 3 August 1970 & 18 August 1980, (2 t.l.s. (with related material) (Box 11, Folder 401)
    - American Festival of Negro Arts To John Howard Griffin, New York, 4 March 1965 - 25 July 1970, (7 t.l.s., 1 t.l.) (Box 11, Folder 402)
      [Many signed by R.S. Pritchard, pianist-composer.
    - Sheed & Ward Correspondence re. Thirteen for Christ (Box 12, Folder 403)
      [Re. Griffin's essay on Dr. Martin Luther King
    - Progressive Magazine "Why They Can't Wait: An Interview with a White Negro", July 1954, (6 page photocopy) (Box 12, Folder 404)
      [Interview with Bradford Daniel
    - Dubay, Father William To John Howard Griffin, Anaheim, CA, 26 September - 22 December 1964, (2 a.l.s., 1 t.l.s.) (Box 12, Folder 405)
      [Re. racism in Los Angeles and the attitude of Cardinal McIntyre
    - Letters and manuscripts relating to racism in Los Angeles, CA, 1962-1964, (1 t.l.s., 1 t.l., 1 a.l.s., 1 2, t.ms. ) (Box 12, Folder 406)
    - Griffin's letter to Cardinal McIntyre, Mansfield, TX, 7 July 1964, (2 page t.l. (carbon) (Box 12, Folder 407)
    - Halsell, Grace To John Howard Griffin, Washington, D.C., 8 - 30 April 1968, (3 t.l.s., 1 t.n.) (Box 12, Folder 408)
      [The white woman who "became" a black woman and wrote about her experiences in her book was Soul Sister. In these letters, as well as in her book, she cites Griffin as her inspiration for the project; she sought and received his counsel and support.
    - Penn Jones Jr., critic of the Warren Commission, author of the series of books, Forgive My Grief (4 volumes); his findings about the strange deaths after Dallas were featured in a major cover story in Ramparts; included here are photocopies of Griffin's "Preface" to the first volume of Forgive My Grief and Griffin's photographs of Jones for that book as well as H.C. Nash's biography of Jones, Citizen's Arrest (Latitudes Press); plus Ramparts feature. (Box 12, Folder 409)
    - Palfi, Marion To John Howard Griffin, Ojai & Loa Angeles, CA, 13 Aug. 1965 - 25 Feb. 1967, (5 t.l.s. (with related carbon) (Box 12, Folder 410)
      [Photographer and friend of Berenice Abbott
    - Southwest Review To John Howard Griffin, Dallas, TX, 3 Nov. 1961 - 5 Feb. 1962, (3 t.l.s (signed Margaret Hartley) (Box 12, Folder 411)
      [With carbons by Griffin
    - Bradshaw, Father J. To John Howard Griffin, Toronto, Canada, 4 Jan.1962, (1 page t.l.s. (with carbon reply) (Box 12, Folder 412)
      [Editor of The Basilian Teacher, re. the publication of the essay "The Men From the Boys," a piece about writing
    - Neslova, Zara To John Howard Griffin, New York, 22 March 1962, (2 page a.l.s. (with 3 Griffin carbons) (Box 12, Folder 413)
      [Nelsova was a musician Griffin had long admired, and he made arrangements to take a portrait photograph of her
  - Subseries XII.3: Media
    Catholic magazines; Correspondences with publishers concerning the use of his photographic portraits; Newspaper features and news stories on Griffin from the 1960s; Correspondences with magazine editors regarding published (as well as unpublished) articles--on racism--by Griffin; and much more miscellaneous business mail about his work.. This section includes more than 50 letters (original typescripts on various media stationery) to Griffin, as well as many of his responses (carbon typescripts). Because of Black Like Me and Griffin's extensive lecture tours speaking against racism, there was a tremendous spin-off of his work in the form of magazine articles, as well as many features about his work and life.
    - Catholic magazine articles on John Howard Griffin [photocopies], (26 folders ) (Box 12, Folder 414)
    - Correspondence with magazines (Box 12, Folder 415)
    - Doubleday & Co. To John Howard Griffin, New York, 14 June 1965, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 12, Folder 416)
    - Harper & Brothers To John Howard Griffin, New York, 28 March 1962, (1 page t.l.s. (with carbon reply) (Box 12, Folder 417)
    - University of Iowa To John Howard Griffin, Iowa City, 13 March 1969 & 16 Feb. 1970, (2 t.l.s. (with carbon) (Box 12, Folder 418)
    - Glinski, Mateo To John Howard Griffin, Ontario & Detroit, 21 Dec. 1963 - 27 Feb. 1966, (6 t.l.s. (with related material) (Box 12, Folder 419)
      [Polish conductor re. Chopin
    - Show [magazine] To John Howard Griffin, New York, 29 Jan. & 8 Feb. 1962, (2 t.l.s. (with carbons) (Box 12, Folder 420)
    - National Geographic Society To John Howard Griffin, Washington, DC, 28 Nov. 1961, (1 page t.l.s.) (Box 12, Folder 421)
    - Darton, Longman & Todd To John Howard Griffin, London, 9 Nov. 1965, (1 page t.l.s. (with related material) (Box 12, Folder 422)
    - Healey, Father Augustine To John Howard Griffin, San Antonio, TX, 26 May 1965 - 7 July 1966, (6 t.l.s.) (Box 12, Folder 423)
    - Hill & Wang To John Howard Griffin, New York, 9 July 1963, (1 t.l.s. (with carbon reply) (Box 12, Folder 424)
    - Newspaper article on Griffin [photocopies] (Box 12, Folder 425)
    - Holt, Reinhart & Winston Memorandum of agreement (Box 12, Folder 426)
    - Miscellaneous literary business letters (Box 12, Folder 427)
    - Teachers College Record To John Howard Griffin, New York, 16 Feb. 1962, (1 page t.l.s. (with carbon) (Box 12, Folder 428)
    - Southern Methodist University To John Howard Griffin, Dallas, TX, 6 March 1962, (1 page t.l.s. (with carbon) (Box 12, Folder 429)
    - Wilson Library Bulletin Biographical sketch of John Howard Griffin, New York, May 1963, (1 page article) (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Subseries XII.4: Censorship
    - Rossett, Barney To John Howard Griffin, New York, 5 April 1952, (1 t.l.s. 1, statement (with related carbons) ) (Box 12, Folder 431)
      [Rossett, publisher of Grove Press, solicited Griffin's support on behalf of Henry Miller's Tropic of Cancer, which was cleared of the charge of pornography by the Supreme Court, on February 21, 1962; there is a carbon typescript of Griffin's reply of support, as well as related documents.
    - Griffin's Letter to The House Committee Investigating Textbooks attacking the censorship group, Texans For America, Mansfield, TX, 1 February 1962, (1 page t.l. (carbon) (Box 12, Folder 432)
    - Boller, Paul To John Howard Griffin, Dallas, TX, 24 Jan. 1962 - 16 Feb. 1962, (4 t.l.s. (with related carbons) (Box 12, Folder 433)
      [Re. Texans for America
    - Carroll, Lucile C. To John Howard Griffin, Midland, TX, 29 Jan. 1962, (2 p[age t.l.s. (with relater material) (Box 12, Folder 434)
      [Concerning the removal of 1984, Steinbeck, and others from the library shelves.
    - Allison, James To John Howard Griffin, Midland, TX, 26 Jan. 1962, (1 page t.l.s. (with related carbons) (Box 12, Folder 435)
    - American Book Publishers Council To John Howard Griffin, New York, 31 Jan. 1962, (1 page t.l.s. (with related carbon) (Box 12, Folder 436)
    - Olan, Rabbi Levy A. The Harm That Good Men Do, Dallas, TX, 12 Nov. 1961, (3 page t.ms. (copy, with related carbon) (Box 12, Folder 437)
    - Wardlaw, Frank H. To John Howard Griffin, 9 Feb. 1962, 1 page, (t.l.s. ) (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Subseries XII.5: Painting & Photography
    - Ellis, Robert C. & Rosa Ellis To John Howard Griffin, Mexico & New York, 4 April 1963 - 28 May 1965, (7 a.l.s., 5 t.l.s.) (Box 12, Folder 439)
      [Robert Ellis, whom Griffin considered one of the great modern American painters, shared a long personal friendship with the writer. The Ellises and the Griffins were inseparable friends for twenty years. Ellis died in 1979, the year before Griffin. Rosa Ellis manages a gallery in Taos, NM.. All these letters are from the early 1960s. According the Elizabeth Griffin, the correspondence from 1965-1979, on both sides, was accidentally destroyed.
    - Griffin, John Howard To Robert C. Ellis, Mansfield, TX, 25 Feb. 1962 - 7 Aug. 1963, (7 t.l. (carbon) (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Catalogs of Ellis Shows and articles on Ellis (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - Dorr, Nell To John Howard Griffin, Washington, CT, 22 Feb. 1966 - 3 Oct. 1967, (24 a.l.s., 5 a.p.c.s.) (Box 12, Folder 442-444)
      [Edward Steichen raved about in U.S. Camera (in 1939), was one of America's greatest photographers. Her magnificent books, The Bare Feet (about Mexican-peasants) and Mother and Child are the most original, lyrical works we have. She worked without a light meter and with very simple cameras, learning photography by trial and error. In 1968, Griffin gave her a light meter, quite astonished that she had achieved such mastery of light without the instrument. Griffin considered Nell Dorr the supreme American photographer. He took many lovely portraits of her which have not been published.
    - Photocopies of articles on Nell Dorr (Box 13, Folder 445)
    - Craeybeckx, A. S. H. "Of Night and Day." Article on Nell Dorr (translated from French by Griffin), Photo Tribune, Nov. 1969, (5 page t.ms. (photocopy) (Box 13, Folder 446)
    - Loache, Benjamin De To John Howard Griffin, New Haven, CT, 11 June 1967, (2 page a.l.s.) (Box 13, Folder 447)
    - Beecher, John To John Howard Griffin, Santa Clara & New Orleans, 30 Jan. 1964 - 17 March 1966, (5 t.l.s. (with related carbon) (Box 13, Folder 448)
    - Stout, W.W. To John Howard Griffin, Hattiesburg, MI, 26 July - 1 Aug. 1963, (3 t.l.s.) (Box 13, Folder 449)
      [Re. Jim Whitmore
    - Griffin, John Howard Essay on Photography, [Mexico?], [1960s], (8 page t.ms.) (Box 13, Folder 450)
- Series XIII: The Thomas Merton File
  The close friendship of Thomas Merton and John Howard Griffin is detailed by Griffin in his "Prologue" to Follow the Ecstasy; as well, there is a discussion of their affinities in Robert Bonazzi's "Foreword" to the Orbis Books edition of Follow the Ecstasy. The correspondence focuses on a wide range of subjects--race relations, the Vietnam War, major change in the Church under Pope John XXIII, and their mutual friendship with French philosopher Jacques Maritain, etc. The most discussed subject, however, turned out to be Merton's new-found passion for photography, which was greatly encouraged by Griffin (who gave the monk a good camera and processed his negatives).
  - Subseries XIII.1: General Correspondence
    - Merton, Thomas To John Howard Griffin, Trappist, KY, & Bangkok, Thailand, 1962 - 1968, (4 a.l.s. 8 a.p.c.s. 37 t.l.s. 5 t.p.c.s.) (Box 13, Folder 452-456)
      [Letter, dated November 9, 1968, is an Original Typescript on the letterhead of the Hotel Imperial in New Delhi. His last letter to Griffin was on the letterhead of The Oriental Hotel, Bangkok, dated December 7, 1968 (just three days before his death on Dec 10). Also, the envelope from that last letter, as well as a photographic packet Merton mailed from Thailand.
    - Griffin, John Howard To Thomas Merton, Mansfield & Fort Worth, TX, 1962-1967, (12 t.l. (carbon) (Box 13, Folder 457)
    - Abbey of Gethsemani Cards (8) re. Merton and Dom James Fox (Box 13, Folder 458)
    - Dom James Fox To John Howard Griffin, Trappist, KY, 1963 - 1971, (9 t.l.s., 1 a.l.s.) (Box 13, Folder 459)
      [Dom James was Merton Is Abbot, with whom the monk had a long, personal, and sometimes confrontational relationship; also the Abbot who allowed Merton to live in a hermitage, beginning in 1965, as the first monk to become a hermit in the Cistercian Order since the Middle Ages
    - Griffin, John Howard To Dom James Fox, TX, 1963-1971, (5 t.l. (carbon) (Box 13, Folder 460)
      [Re. the Abbot's permission for Griffin to photograph Merton in 1963 and discussion of the Fox-Merton relationship after the monk's death; out of Griffin's 1963 photo session with the monk came the 'Official Portrait'
    - Palivic, Tom To John Howard Griffin, Louisville, KY, 19 Oct. 1975, (2 page a.l.s. (with carbon reply) (Box 13, Folder 461)
    - Three Homilies for the Funeral Mass of Abbot Fox, by Dom Flavian Burns (the succeeding Abbot), Brother Patrick Hart, and Father Matthew Kelty (Box 13, Folder 462)
    - Brother Patrick Hart To John Howard Griffin, Trappist, KY, 1966-1980 (Box 13, Folder 463 &464)
      [Brother Hart was Merton's secretary in 1968; he has become the most knowledgeable Merton scholar today, publishing several anthologies by or about Merton, as well as being the General Editor for the Merton Journals (withheld from the public for 25 years after the monk's death; the first volumes will be published in 1994).
    - Griffin, John Howard To Brother Patrick Hart, Fort Worth, TX, 1969-1973, (7 t.l. (carbon), 1 t.p.c.s., 1 t.n.) (Box 13, Folder 465)
    - Father John Eudes Bamberger To John Howard Griffin, Las Condes, Chile & Trappist, KY, 19 Feb. & 27 May [n.y.], (2 a.l.s.) (Box 13, Folder 466)